elitehost.co.za 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy | Elitehost Web Hosting, Reseller Hosting, VPS and Domains by Elitehost

#### 1\. Introduction

The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to customers what types of information we will collect and how that information is used. In most cases, we collect this information to ensure network integrity and that we continue to provide you with the most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some cases, we are required by law to collect personal information about customers. Except where the law requires otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data.

#### 2\. Confidentiality

Elitehost, a division of Optify Systems (Pty) Ltd respects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our website, or those websites hosted by us. We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and users including all personal information supplied in the course of contracting with us for services. We undertake not to sell your personal information to third parties for commercial or marketing purposes.

#### 3\. Collection of Personal Data

Elitehost, a division of Optify Systems (Pty) Ltd collects personal data about our users when you visit a website hosted by us; apply for a hosting package or domain and through theuse of cookie technology.

#### 4\. Cookies

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired.

#### 5\. Use of Personal Data

Elitehost, a division of Optify Systems (Pty) Ltd may on occasion use your personal information to contact you to advise you of matters relevant to service provision and in some cases, solicit your feedback. We do not pass on any personal details to 3rd parties for any promotional purposes.

We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties - for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.

Any information Elitehost collects from you through correspondence with us, whether via e-mail, telephonically or by written letter, will only be used to address the matters within that correspondence. If this requires referring such correspondence within Elitehost or to a third party to ensure customer service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address your query or concerns, and will otherwise be kept confidential.

#### 6\. Reservation of Rights

Elitehost reserves the right to disclose information about customers where required in good faith, to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal claims.

Elitehost further reserves the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate or prevent illegal activities being committed over our network

#### 7\. Changes to this Policy

Elitehost, a division of Optify Systems (Pty) Ltd reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it. Where a major change is made, customers will be informed by e-mail notification or through a notice on our website. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates as the case may be.

#### 8\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please contact management@elitehost.co.za. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details from any list under our control.
